[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many types of blood vessels are there?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "6", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An emblem of what saint does the little girl give to John in the 2004 action drama movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "St. Jude", "incorrect_answers": ["St. Luke", "St. Jonh", "St. Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name used for black tea in Chinese, Korean and Japanese languages?", "correct_answer": "Crimson tea", "incorrect_answers": ["Grey tea", "Purple tea", "Brown tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This seemingly lifelike substance is allegedly extruded from the bodies of mediums. It can be vaporous or solid and is said to smell of ozone. What is it?", "correct_answer": "Ectoplasm", "incorrect_answers": ["Plasma", "Endoplasm", "Cytoplasm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Yippee-Ki-Yay  *#%^#%  is a quote used by Det. John McClane in which series of police thrillers?", "correct_answer": "Die Hard", "incorrect_answers": ["Legal Weapon", "Dirty Harry", "The Naked Gun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The National Aeronautics and Space Administration was established on July 29, 1958 under which U.S.  President?", "correct_answer": "Dwight Eisenhower", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Truman", "John Kennedy", "Lyndon Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these stars does not have a cameo in Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas?", "correct_answer": "Jim Carrey", "incorrect_answers": ["Tobey Maguire", "Gary Busey", "Cameron Diaz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Muppet Show was banned in Saudi Arabia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This substance is a substitute for sugar that can help prevent tooth decay. It decreases plaque formation and blocks the bacteria from producing the acids that cause cavities.", "correct_answer": "Xylitol", "incorrect_answers": ["Aspartame", "NutraSweet", "Dentin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the 77th Academy Awards, The Incredibles lost the award for best animated feature to Shrek 2 .", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The use of puppets for animation was first developed in this country.", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Italy", "Belgium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of Rizzo, one of the female characters in the film Grease?", "correct_answer": "Betty", "incorrect_answers": ["Bonnie", "Margaret", "Belinda"]}]